你在想什么
What are you thinking about?
昨天的事
Yesterday.
扎克  我无能为力
Zack. I can't stop.
我也是
Yeah, me neither.
石头  剪刀  布
以前人海茫茫
It used to be we all had acquaintances.
朋友来来往往
Just people moving in and out of your life.
没什么大不了的
No big.
以后还会再见到他们
See them down the road sometime.
但现在
Now...
你只认识几个人
a handful of people you know,
仅此而已
and that's it.
他们可能是世界上仅存的人类
They might as well be the only people left in the world.
我是不是话很多
Am I talking too much?
有点吧  但我喜欢
A little, but I like it.
? I got you ?
? 爱你 ?
? Under my skin ?
? 已入骨 ?
? I got you ?
? 爱你 ?
? Deep in the heart of me ?
? 到心坎里 ?
现在你是在让我难堪了
Okay, now you're just embarrassing me.
? So deep in my heart ?
? 深埋心间 ?
? That you are really a part of me ?
? 不分离 ?
我爱你
I got you.
我们该休息了
We should probably try to get some rest.
来我房里睡吧
Hey, come crash at my place.
好吧  那我去你那睡
Okay, I'll crash at your place, then.
我们一旦开始就不会停了
You know we start doing that, we're not gonna want to stop.
现在还不行
Not just yet.
晚安
Good night.
尼克
区
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新请登陆www.YYeTs.com
翻译  冰蓝
翻译  33来了
翻译  Reginamoon
翻译  重案组李Sir
翻译  卫老哥
翻译  鱼小姐啦
翻译  小饭
翻译  送小孩
校对  Lemony  送小孩
校对  冰蓝  米小勒
时间轴  加森
时间轴  marktaotao
特效/后期  、青衣
时间轴/特效/后期  吉吉
总监  Lemony  送小孩
行尸走肉
第四季  第二集
区
■
卡尔
Carl?
Carl.
起床了
Come on.
抱歉
Sorry.
该换岗了吗
Changing of the guard?
是啊
Yeah.
检查完周边后我给你带早饭
I'll bring you breakfast after perimeter check.
天啊  扔掉吧
Oh, my God. Throw that away.
想都别想
Not gonna happen.
是我的了
It's mine.
出去小心点
Careful out there.
我一向很小心  要什么
Always am. Any requests?
书  漫画  变味的MM豆
Books? Comics? Some stale M&Ms?
你才喜欢变味的MM豆
You're the one that likes stale M&Ms.
那我肯定要找一些
Then I'll definitely looking for some.
我也会找些你喜欢的东西
I'll look for some stuff you like, too.
你怎么不戴帽子了
Why don't you wear your hat anymore?
那不是农夫帽  回头见吧
It's not a farming hat. See you soon?
很快就能见
Pretty soon.
他们昨天只干掉了一群
They only took out one cluster yesterday.
也许今天需要更多人手
Probably gonna need more people today.
我们也许能帮忙
Maybe we could help.
我有其他计划
I got other plans
那就是靠泥土和黄瓜
involving dirt and cucumbers
让人们丰衣足食
and keeping people fed.
如果你不想帮忙  我倒是想去
Well, if you don't want to, maybe I could.
行吗
Could I?
或许我该说
We have other plans.
是"我们俩"有其他计划
That's what I should have said.
来吧  多吃点
Come on in. There we go.
老爸
Dad...?
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我一直在努力
I've been trying.
我知道  也为你骄傲
Yeah, I know. And I'm proud.
老爸
Dad,
什么时候能把枪还给我
when can I have my gun back?
虫子能给它们补充蛋白质
Worms will give them some extra protein.
跟紧点
Stay close.
救命  快救救我们
Help! Help! Please, come quick!
-牢房区那边吗  -我不知道
- Cell block? - I don't know.
跟玛姬到塔里去  别磨蹭快去
Get in the tower with Maggie. Don't argue, go.
-D区有行尸  -那C区呢
- Walkers in D! - What about C?
安全  我们已经把通往墓地的门锁了
Clear. We locked the gates to the tombs.
-赫谢尔在值岗  -那就不是缺口的事
- Hershel's on guard. - It ain't a breach.
我们按计划行事
We followed the plan.
天呐
Whoa, boy.
坚持住
Hold on!
站起来
Come here.
-快走  -达里尔
- Move! - Daryl!
我来了  你没事吧
I got it. Are you bit?
快走  快出去
Go. Get out of here.
拿着枪  快走
Hold that. Go, go.
被咬了吗  快出去
Are you bit? All right, go.
快起来  躲到牢房里
Get up. Get back in the cell.
抱着
Here.
跟我来
Follow me!
跟我走  待在里面
Come with me. Stay in there.
等等  等等
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
抱紧了  走
Got you. Go!
凯伦  凯伦
Karen! Karen!
-你没事吧  -还好吧
- Are you okay? - You all right?
保持冷静
Just stay calm.
我得给你截肢  免得感染扩散
I'm gonna have to amputate your arm to stop the infection from spreading.
把牢房全部查一遍
Check all of 'em-- every cell.
我马上给你做手术
I have to do it now.
你把这个咬住
I want you to bite this.
-下面安全了吧  -对
- Are we clear down here? - Yeah.
-我们安全了吗  -是的
- We're safe? - Yeah, yeah.
上来
Up here!
没事了
It's okay.
蹲下
Get down!
谢了
Thanks.
天呐  是帕特里克
Oh, it's Patrick.
都是他们区的人
That's all of 'em.
我开始变异了  对不对
It's happening, isn't it?
你受到了惊吓
You're in shock, okay?
我想让你好好躺着
I want you just to lay back.
丽兹和米卡
Lizzie and Mica,
你关心她们
you care about them.
我亲眼见过
I've seen it.
我没有其他亲人了
I don't have anybody else.
孩子们靠自己的话
Kids on their own,
无法活下去
they don't have a chance.
你能照顾她们吗
Can you look out for them?
视如己出
Like they're yours?
能
Yeah.
我能
Yeah, I can.
我会的
I will.
瑞恩
Ryan.
你得让她们来跟你告别
You're gonna have to let them say goodbye.
好吗
Okay?
好的
Okay.
没被咬  没受伤
No bites. No wounds.
他是正常死亡
I think he just died.
死得很惨  吸入性胸膜炎
Horribly, too. Pleurisy aspiration.
被自己的血液呛死
Choked to death on his own blood.
所以脸上全是血
Caused those trails down his face.
我在栅栏外的行尸
I've seen them before
脸上见到过
on a walker outside the fences.
我也在帕特里克脸上见过
I saw them on Patrick, too.
因肺内的压力不断增加
They're from the internal lung pressure building up--
好比你摇一瓶汽水  就会把瓶盖崩开
like if you shake a soda can and pop the top.
你的眼睛
Only imagine your eyes,
耳朵  鼻子和喉咙好比瓶盖
ears, nose, and throat are the top.
是被行尸传染的吗
It's a sickness from the walkers?
不是  它们出现之前就有这种病
No, these things happened before they were around.
可能是肺炎球菌
Could be pneumococcal.
很可能是一种急性流感
Most likely an aggressive flu strain.
有人及时把他关了起来
Someone locked him in just in time.
不是  查理经常梦游
No, man. Charlie used to sleepwalk.
是他把自己锁起来的  他昨天还吃烤肉来着
Locked himself in. Hell, he was just eating barbecue yesterday.
怎么会有人得了感冒一天就死了
How could somebody die in a day just from a cold?
有头猪病了  死得很快
I had a sick pig, it died quick.
我在林子里见过一头病死的野猪
Saw a sick boar in the woods.
猪和禽类  过去疾病都是通过这些动物传染的
Pigs and birds. That's how these things spread in the past.
我们得处理一下那些猪
We need to do something about those hogs.
可能我们很幸运  只有这么两例
Maybe we got lucky. Maybe these two cases are it.
这年头没人幸运
Haven't seen anybody be lucky in a long time.
病菌容易近距离传播
Bugs like to run through close quarters.
不要离他再近了
Doesn't get any closer than this.
我们在这里  已接触了病菌
All of us in here, we've all been exposed.
爸爸
Dad?
我们得去找S医生
We have to go get Dr. S.
亲爱的  他被咬了
Honey, he's been bit.
医生也帮不了他
The doctor won't help.
你要照顾好你妹妹
You take care of your sister.
爸爸
Dad.
Dad?
-爸爸  -不要
- Dad? - No.
-走吧  时候到了  -不要
- Come on, it's time. - No.
你们知道我要怎么做
You know what I have to do.
这是惯例
What we're always supposed to do.
你们可以在外面等
You can wait outside if you want.
好吗
Okay?
应该由我们来做
We should be the ones.
不  我做不到
No. I can't.
丽兹  你确定吗
Lizzie, are you sure?
你教过我们
You taught us.
我能做到的
I can do it.
好吧  但是你现在就得动手了
Okay, well, you have to do it now.
你立刻就得动手
You need to do it right now
得赶在他尸变前
because you have to do it before he turns.
我就待在这儿
I'm gonna stay right here.
你记得我怎么教你们的吗
You remember what I showed you?
丽兹  丽兹  丽兹
Lizzie. Lizzie, Lizzie.
没事的  没事了
It's okay. It's okay.
丽兹  丽兹  没事了  深呼吸
Lizzie? Lizzie, it's okay. Breathe.
看着那些花
Look at the flowers.
和我一起数  一  二  三
Count one, two, three with me.
-一  二  -爸爸  不要啊
- One, two-- - Daddy, no!
别看  丽兹  看着这些花
No, Lizzie, look at the flowers.
和我数  一  二  三
Count one, two, three with me.
一  二  三
One, two, three.
看着这些花  丽兹
Look at the flowers, Lizzie.
-不要  -看着这些花
- No! - Look at the flowers!
区
先别靠近我
Hey, you might want to stay back.
-卡尔  -爸爸  对不起
- Carl. - Dad, I'm sorry.
我没看见你出来
I didn't see you come out.
没事了  我出来了
It's okay. I'm here.
我没事  离远点
I'm fine. Back away.
我不得已用了一支大门边上的枪
I had to use one of the guns by the gate.
我发誓我不想的
I swear I didn't want to.
我往回走的时候摔倒了
I was coming back. I fell.
他们跑出来救了我
They came out and helped me.
你没事吧
Are you all right?
里面发生了什么
What happened in there?
帕特里克昨晚生病了
Patrick got sick last night.
是某种流感  发作得很急
It's some kind of flu. It moves fast.
我们认为是他死了  然后攻击了牢房
We think he died and attacked the cell block.
我知道他是你的朋友  我很抱歉
Look, I know he was your friend and I'm sorry.
他是个好孩子
He was a good kid.
我们失去了很多好人
We lost a lot of good people.
格伦和你爸爸都没事
Glenn and your dad are okay,
但是他们之前都在里面
but they were in there.
你不应该离任何可能被感染的人太近
You shouldn't get too close to anyone that might have been exposed,
至少一段时间内不要
at least for a little while.
卡尔  你们三个都是
Carl. All of you.
帕特里克昨天还好好的
Patrick was fine yesterday,
隔夜就死了
and he died overnight.
两个人死的那么快
Two people died that quick?
我们得把所有接触过的人隔离
We'll have to separate everyone that's been exposed.
那就是刚进牢房区的所有人了
That's everyone in that cell block.
我们所有人  也许更多
That's all of us. Maybe more.
我们知道这种疾病可能致命
We know that this sickness can be lethal.
但我们不知道它的传染性有多强
We don't know how easily it spreads.
还有其他人表现出我们知道的症状吗
Is anyone else showing symptoms that we know of?
我们不能干等着  还有孩子呢
We can't just wait and see. There's children.
不仅仅是疾病的问题
It isn't just the illness.
人一死还会成为威胁
If people die, they become a threat.
我们需要给他们找个地方
We need a place for them to go.
他们不能待在D区
They can't stay in D.
我们不能冒险进去清扫
We can't risk going in there to clean it up.
我们可以用A区
We can use cell block A.
死囚区吗
Death row?
我可不觉得那里更好
I'm not sure that's much of an upgrade.
那里很干净  所以更好
It's clean. That's an upgrade.
S医生应该没问题吧
Think that'll work for Dr. S?
我可以帮迦勒一起整理
I'll help Caleb get it set up.
-你还好吗  -没事
- You okay? - Mm-hmm.
你确定吗  听起来可不怎么好
You sure? You don't sound so good.
我带她去我的房间  让她休息一下
We're just taking her back to my cell so she can rest.
泰尔西  那不是好主意
Tyreese, I don't think that's a good idea.
为什么  这是怎么了
Why? What's going on now?
我们觉得可能是流感之类的
We think it's a flu or something.
帕特里克就那么死的
That's how Patrick died.
朱迪思在那个牢房区
Judith was in that cell block.
她很脆弱
She's vulnerable.
任何可能已经病了
Anyone that may be sick
或者可能被感染的人都应该离远点
or even exposed should stay away.
-帕特里克死于这个病吗  -她会没事的
- It killed Patrick? - She's gonna be okay.
既然我们知道帕特里克的死因
Now that we know what Patrick died from
那我们就有办法解决  对吗
we can treat it, right?
别慌  我们会搞清楚的
Don't panic. We're going to figure this out.
但与此同时我们需要把你隔离
But we should keep you separated in the meantime.
我会让迦勒去看看你
We'll have Caleb take a look at you.
我看看有没有什么药物治疗的方法
I'll see what we have in the way of medications.
迪凯特组的大卫
David from the Decatur group,
他也在咳嗽
he's been coughing, too.
我去找他
I'll get him.
坟墓那边还有干净的空房间吧
There's some empty clean cells in the tombs, right?
-对  我们在那里碰头  -好
- Yeah, we'll meet you there. - Okay.
来吧
Come on.
我们去把你安顿好
Let's get you settled.
待会儿还得开会
Have to call another meeting later.
好
All right.
我要去埋死人
I'll get to burying the dead ones.
记得戴手套和面罩
You wear gloves and a mask.
你还好吗
You all right?
我很担心丽兹和米卡
I'm worried about Lizzie and Mica.
他们在帕特里克身边待过
They were around Patrick.
我们都待过
We all were.
凯伦和大卫在情况好转前都先隔离
Karen and David are gonna be separated till they feel better.
-说的对  -你没事吧
- You're right. - Are you okay?
不能有事啊
Mm-hmm. Got to be.
得把你爸爸埋了
Gonna bury your dad.
你可以来看看他  给他带点花
You can visit, bring him flowers.
丽兹  我们得谈谈里头发生的事
Lizzie, we're gonna have to talk about what happened in there.
你爸爸叫我对你视如己出  我会做到的
Your daddy asked me to protect you like you're my own and I will.
是时候跟你说实话了
It's time someone told you the truth.
亲爱的  你不够坚强
Honey, you're weak.
你当时完全吓坏了
You lost your nerve.
你得一直勇敢果断才行
You have to trust your gut and you have to act fast every time.
这攸关生死
That's life and death.
他死了
He's dead.
我知道  很遗憾
I know, and I'm sorry.
但如果你想活下去  就得坚强起来
But if you want to live, you have to become strong.
他死了
He's dead.
他死了  他是我爸爸可他现在死了
He's dead.He was special and now he's dead.
他们为什么要杀他  为什么要杀尼克
Why'd they kill him? Why'd they kill Nick?
你太傻了
You're so stupid.
尼克
Nick?
她只是脑子有点乱
She's messed up.
她很坚强
She's not weak.
很高兴你当时在那儿
Glad you were in there.
没了枪  我也没啥用
Wasn't much use without my gun.
你贡献很大
No, you were.
这一次你经受住了考验
All this time you've been taking off,
大家有目共睹
you earned it.
没你我们也走不到现在
We wouldn't be here without you.
这是大家共同的努力
It was all of us.
不  是在你的领导下
No, it was you first.
你要再带我们挺过这一回吗
You gonna help us figure this out?
我搞砸了太多次
I screwed up too many times.
你不得不替我照应  而我沉湎于悲痛
Those calls you got to make, I start down that road...
我差点害我儿子性情大变
I almost lost my boy-- who he was.
如果有别的需要  我可以挺身而出
Whatever else this place needs, I'm here for it.
我说过了  你经受住了考验
Like I said, you earned it.
无论如何  你能看出问题
But for what it's worth, you see mistakes.
麻烦来的时候
I see when the shit hits,
你也能拿着铁锹守在那儿
you're standing there with a shovel.
瑞克  达里尔
Rick! Daryl!
见鬼
Oh, shit.
声响太大把它们都引来了  这儿快不行了
The noise drew 'em out and now this part's starting to give.
你看到什么了吗
Did you see anything?
他们开始把死人搬出来
They just started taking out the dead.
我不知道谁死了
I don't need to know who yet.
我也不想知道
I don't want to.
很高兴你安全回来
I'm glad you came back safe.
太傻了
It was stupid.
我太傻了
I was so stupid.
我摔倒的时候  他们就该抛下我不管
When I fell on my ass, they should have just left me out there.
这是傻话
Now that's stupid.
我们在乎你
We care about you.
他们可能会受伤
They could have gotten hurt.
你在乎一个人时
When you care about people
受伤是在所难免的
hurt is kind of part of the package.
有孩子吗
Were there any kids?
寡妇和孤儿都有称呼
Got all these widows and orphans,
但要怎么称呼失去孩子的人
but what do you call someone who lost a child?
会有人给那类人起名字吗
You'd think someone would have given that a name.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
她常那样哭吗
Does she always cry like that?
我觉得她能感知人们的情绪
I think she senses people's moods.
别
Don't.
我们应该远离彼此
We're supposed to stay away from each other.
你们看到这个了吗
Are you seeing this?
有人在喂行尸吗
Is someone feeding these things?
-当心  -快顶住这边的栅栏
- Heads up. - This part of the fence, now!
等等  等等
Hold on, hold on.
快倒了  快倒了
It's gonna give! It's gonna give!
所有人退后  快点  退后
Everybody back! Come on, back, now.
栅栏继续往里凹陷的话
Fence keeps bending in like that,
行尸会闯进来的
those walkers are coming over it.
达里尔  把车开过来
Daryl, get the truck.
我知道该怎么办
I know what to do.
帕特里克是不是天主教徒
You know if Patrick was Catholic?
他说他是无神论者
He said he was a practicing atheist.
你告诉你爸昨天图书馆的事了吗
Did you tell your dad what you saw in the library yesterday?
没
Nope.
你会告诉他吗
Are you going to tell him?
我必须教那些孩子们如何生存
I have to keep teaching those kids to survive.
你懂的
You know that.
你告诉他们父母了吗
Did you tell their parents?
没有
No.
你会告诉他们吗
Are you gonna tell them?
如果我说了  这事过后他们也许会理解
If I do, maybe after this they'll understand.
但他们也许不会  我不想这个冒险
But maybe they won't. I don't want to take that risk.
那是你们之间的问题
That's between you and them.
不
No.
这是我们之间的问题
It's between you and me.
如果你告诉你爸  他就会告诉家长
If you tell your dad, he'll tell them.
如我所说  他们也许会理解  也许不会
And like I said, maybe they'll understand, maybe they won't.
我不想对我爸撒谎
I don't want to lie to my dad.
我没让你撒谎
I'm not asking you to lie.
我让你别告诉他
I'm asking you not to say anything.
? Lying in my bed at night ?
? 夜卧床榻 ?
? I don't wanna grow up ?
? 不愿长大 ?
? Nothin' ever seems to turn out right ?
? 事事与愿违 ?
? I don't wanna grow up ?
? 我不愿长大 ?
? How do you move in a world of fog ?
? 世间充满迷雾 ?
? That's always changing things ?
? 一切变幻莫测 ?
? Makes me wish that I could be a dog ?
? 宁为犬  勿为人 ?
? When I see the price that you pay ?
? 物是人已非 ?
? I don't wanna grow up ?
? 我不愿长大 ?
? Nothin' ever seems to go that way ?
? 事事与愿违 ?
? I don't want to grow up ?
? 我不愿长大 ?
? Only thing to live for is today ?
? 活在当下... ?
这摇篮曲真不错
Some lullaby.
我给她唱我喜欢的歌
I just sing her what I like.
总比给她唱
Figure it's better than ashes
吓人的歌谣要好些
or cradles falling out of trees.
-糟糕  你能抱会儿她吗  -贝丝  不
- Oh, shoot. Can you hold her a second?  - Beth. Beth!
-拜托了  我满身都是萝卜渣  -不
- Please, I'm covered in carrots. - No.
谢谢
Thanks.
准备好了吗
Ready?
开始吧
Let's go.
走
Go!
好了  停
All right! Hold up!
好了  走
All right, go. Go.
丽兹  它们是行尸
Lizzie, those are walkers.
"尼克"是只行尸
Nick was a walker.
别为行尸死而难过
You don't feel bad about that walker dying.
要为你爸爸难过
You feel bad about your dad.
你爱他  但他走了
You loved him and he's gone.
是啊
Yeah.
好了
There.
我没空
Not this time.
你觉得是猪感染了他们吗
Think the pigs made them sick?
也许是我们感染了猪
Or we made the pigs sick.
我们应该离朱迪远点
I think we should stay away from Judy a while.
-以防万一  -好的
- Just in case. - Okay.
-我也不想这样  但是  -我们必须保护她
- I don't like it, but-- - We have to protect her.
没错
Yes, we do.
-老爸  -嗯
- Hey, Dad. - Yeah?
卡萝尔在教孩子们
Carol's been teaching the kids...
怎么用武器
how to use weapons.
怎么杀行尸
How to kill.
他们的父母不知道
Their parents don't know
她也不想让你知道
and she doesn't want you to know.
我觉得你应该允许她这样做
I think you should let her.
我知道你会说这你无法决定
I know you're gonna say it's not up to you.
但你可以决定
But it can be.
爸
Dad?
谢谢你告诉我
Thank you for telling me.
没事
Yeah.
我不会阻止她
I won't stop her.
不会告诉别人
I won't say anything.
卡尔
Carl?
石头  剪刀  布